<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C on Ponte Posterum</title>
    <link>https://oglinuk.github.io/tags/c/</link>
    <description>Recent content in C on Ponte Posterum</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 11:53:50 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://oglinuk.github.io/tags/c/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PTP</title>
      <link>https://oglinuk.github.io/project/ptp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oglinuk.github.io/project/ptp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vim 1</title>
      <link>https://oglinuk.github.io/post/vim-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 11:53:50 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oglinuk.github.io/post/vim-1/</guid>
      <description>Vim ~ Vimtutor Lesson 1 One of the amazing things about Vim, is that it comes with an interactive tutorial called vimtutor. As the tutorial states, it &amp;ldquo;is designed to describe enough of the commands that you will be able to easily use Vim as an all-purpose editor&amp;rdquo;. It also states &amp;ldquo;this tutor is set up to teach by use. That means that you need to execute the commands to learn them properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hello_c.c</title>
      <link>https://oglinuk.github.io/post/c-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 18:33:38 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oglinuk.github.io/post/c-0/</guid>
      <description>C Well I always new this day was going to come. Originally I was going to learn C++ and not C, but rwxrob has convinced me otherwise. His reasoning? &amp;ldquo;The C programming language is mandatory learning for anyone who truly wants to understand how all languages and digital computers work.&amp;rdquo; [source] For me, the reason why I decided on learning C is because I want to someday contribute to projects I use and love like the Linux kernel, Lynx, Tmux, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quake3 0</title>
      <link>https://oglinuk.github.io/post/quake3-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 08:31:38 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oglinuk.github.io/post/quake3-0/</guid>
      <description>Quake 3 ~ ioquake3 I&amp;rsquo;ve covered DOOM in one of my previous blogs. In this blog I am going to cover how to get Quake 3 arena running. The source port I am going to use is ioquake3. Unlike DOOM, there is no entirely free version of Quake 3. Quake 3 requires .pak files, which can found in the game files after purchasing Quake 3 on steam.
The following dependencies are required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vim 0</title>
      <link>https://oglinuk.github.io/post/vim-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 08:27:35 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oglinuk.github.io/post/vim-0/</guid>
      <description>Vim I was first introduced to Vim by my good friend Sam. As someone who tries to work as much in the terminal as possible, Vim was perfect for my text editing needs. Although I&amp;rsquo;ve known/used Vim for a while, it&amp;rsquo;s always basic usage for quick edititing, and its always been a secondary editor to Visual Studio Code. This was because I relied heavily on the intellisense when programming in langauges like Go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doom 0</title>
      <link>https://oglinuk.github.io/post/doom-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 11:20:58 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oglinuk.github.io/post/doom-0/</guid>
      <description>DOOM DOOM is easily (in my opinion), one of the most iconic games ever made. It is enjoyable to play even to this day. The best part of DOOM is the fact that it has been made open source under a GPL license. From this there have been many source ports of the original DOOM code. I particularly like gzdoom as it adds graphics rending features, but there are quite a few that all have their own unique additions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>